How can you dramatically improve cursor
generate UI from something like this to
something like that? So v 0ero which is
application you probably have been using
to generate really high quality UI for
web application now just released their
own AI model that you can use directly
inside your cursor. They also introduced
some new AI coding workflow that can
make the UI generation much better. Here
is my workflow and setup. So to use
V0ero in your cursor, you actually need
some setup because cursor unfortunately
don't support VZ model natively yet. And
to set up, you will need to go to models
in your cursor settings. For the open AI
base URL, put in
api.vzero.dev/v1. Save it and then go to
your v 0ero chat. Go to settings,
generate API key here, and paste over
into cursor and click verify. You'll
probably be prompt to confirm to enable
open API key here. So from now on, every
time when you choose a GPD based model,
behind the scenes, it actually calling
v0ero model. There's also a bug you will
have that even though you're calling
cloud model but if you have this open AI
API key turned on it will have this
arrow. So making sure you turn off when
you try to use cloud model and turn it
on when you want to use the vzero model.
So as a quick way to showcase the
capability if I just use a 3.7 model and
give a prom make a beautiful calendar
app the result you will get probably
look something like this fully
functional calendar app but the UI of
spacing font color just doesn't look
100%. So instead we can switch model to
GPD 4 and making sure we turn on this
open AI API key here and give the same
problem make beautiful calendar event
app but with one caveat I will just ask
you to build one page to start with cuz
even though vzero model is extremely
good at UI generation it is not as good
in terms of scaffolding the whole
application and complex functionalities.
When I ask you to build a whole
application it often just fail and stuck
in the loop. So I would just ask to
build one page to start with and then
switch to different model. So this is
the result you get one shot from the
Vzero model in cursor. You can see the
UI outcome just looks ton better. All
the spacing font color looks right with
better taste. What's really cool about
it is that you actually don't need to
use Vzero model through the whole DM
process. You can just use that to set a
foundation of how the application should
look like and then we can switch to a
better model like cloud 3.7 or cloud 4
if you want to keep adding new feature
on top of this page. And you might have
this arrow just making sure to turn off
the open API key here and try again.
What you will find is that even though
you switch to different model because VZ
already set a example of what type of
style, spacing, color it should follow,
the new UI generator will follow the
same style and build out all those other
screens that also looks really good. So
this is my current workflow. I will try
to use Vzero to initially set up some
main screens and then use cloud 3.7 or
cloud 4 to build out more functionality.
But if I need to set up some new screen
again or switch back to Vzero to build
out that new screen. This is probably
one of the key benefits I see of Vzero
releasing their own model instead of
just using their chat app because now
you can just switch back and forth
between different model for specific
tasks. So this is a quick example of how
to use the Vzero new model. If you want
to learn more in depths about AI coding,
you can join AI builder club where I
have more advanced tips about AI coding
and building production ready large
learning mode application for myself as
well as industry experts. And we also
have tools that can bootstrap your
building experience from SAS and MCP
template as well as tools like 10X coder
that can turn your vague idea into
wellcraftraft person prd and rules. But
most importantly, we have the community
of top AI builders who are building and
launching their own AI products. So you
can come build with them and get advice.
If you're interested, I put a link in
the description below to join. Thank you
and I see you next